# Sasha Marshall

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & DESIGNER

#### **ABOUT**

Sasha Marshall has 2+ years of experience building web applications and e-commerce platforms. Using MERN stack and Liquid, she creates efficient and effective site functionality. Along with her coding skills, Sasha is also adept in UX/UI design, utilizing Figma and Adobe to optimize user interfaces. Her combined technical and design skills results in practical, user-friendly solutions for any web-based project.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONTEND ENGINEER - Akantro MAY 2023 - CURRENT

- Worked with colleagues, partners, and clients to increase user engagement by building & designing websites and web components.
- Design and implement new apps and web components for clients and partners.
- Use software and languages such as JavaScript, Liquid, CSS, Sass, Tailwind, Figma, Klaviyo, Hydrogen, React, and Node.

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER - Condor OCT 2022 - CURRENT

- Build and maintain websites for small businesses on various platforms such as Wordpress, Shopify, and Squarespace.
- Manage client correspondence and relations.
- Collaborate with colleagues and clients to build functional and efficient sites.
- Utilize Technologies such as Elementor, CSS, JavaScript, and HTML.

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER - Freelance JAN 2022 - CURRENT

- Translate clients wants and needs into efficient and complete sites.
- Dedicated to finding solutions for issues and optimizations to deliver a perfect product.

### CONTACT

(510) 872-3030

https://sashamarshall.dev/sashamarshall.dev@gmail.com

### SKILLS

- MERN Stack; (Mongo DB, Express, React Node)
- Liquid
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Tailwind CSS & Sass
- MVC Paradigm
- GitHub, Git, GitBASH
- Command Line Interfaces
- Postman
- REST API's
- Headless Builds
- npm (Node Package Manager)
- VSCode
- · MacOS and Windows
- · Adobe Suite/Figma/Canva
- · Microsoft Office

### **EDUCATION**

ASSOCIATES OF ARTS

Graduated 2021 San Diego Mesa College